redkaraoke.com 2019-06-26

# RedKaraoke - Privacy and cookie policy

Although [Red Karaoke](https://www.redkaraoke.com/) is an entertainment website to have fun, since we need a record to be able to save the recordings, have a file, etc., we have to give all of that a trustworthy legal coverage that guarantees the use of our users’ data. So here’s the legal text (the “Policy") created by our lawyers.

These Conditions have been drafted in SPANISH. If REDKARAOKE provides a translation in a language other than Spanish, the User accepts that said translation has been provided solely for convenience, and further, that the User’s relationship with REDKARAOKE will be governed exclusively by the version of the Conditions in Spanish.

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

At Planeta Red S.L., which is a Spanish company based at Parque de Santa Juliana 7, local 5, 26004 Logroño La Rioja, CIF B8500760 (hereinafter “We”), we respect your privacy and that of all the users of the services that we offer and are available at both the www.redkaroke.com website and the Sing & Record app by Red Karaoke, the Tu Cara me Suena app by “Red Karaoke” and, in general, all those services we provide and which allow users to sing and record their own karaoke versions of songs and share them on social networks, as well as any other service similar, complementary and/or related to the ones described here (hereinafter all of them referred to as the “Services”) when we collect any data or information that is associated with or may be associated with you individually (hereinafter “Personal Data”) through any system.

This Privacy Policy is applicable to all Personal Data that you may have provided or we may have collected during the use of the Services.

**2\. GATHERING, USAGE, PURPOSE & LEGITIMATION**

To register for the service, you must previously provide certain Personal Data through the applicable forms. If any errors occur during data collection, they will be marked with red asterisks so you can modify them properly. In this sense, you affirm that your data is current and accurate.

Your Personal Data will be included in a automated file owned by us that is registered with the Spanish Agency of data protection and will be subject to automated data processing by us to   
(i) Manage the services and features of the Service, in addition to manage our contractual relationship with you, being the execution of this contract what legitimizes that usage  
(ii) Send commercial communications about products and services similar to the Service that could interest you based on your Personal Data and analyze the effectiveness of the advertising built in our Services, being our legitimate interest in direct marketing what legitimizes that usage At any time, you can tell us that you do not want to continue to receive our commercial communications via regular mail by adjusting your preferences [here](https://www.redkaraoke.com/my-karaoke/notifications)  
(iii) Establish and analyze our customers’ individual, group and behavioral profiles based on our legitimate interest in adapting as much as possible the offer of our services. 

Remember that, in case of agreement, you can revoke it any time addressing to 

The communication of your personal data is a contractual requirement ,so that, in case of not providing them, the service can not be provided by Planeta Red, SL.

In addition, some of our Services adapted for mobile devices or apps may have geolocation features in order to determine, if activated, the location of the devices. Thus, we can collect and process data regarding your location to manage our Services and facilitate the payment of such Services provided that you have activated the geolocation feature on your mobile device, which you can disable at any time. The legal basis for this treatment is the execution of this contract and your expressed consent when activating the geolocation function.

If through any Service feature you provide any third-party data, you guarantee that you have obtained the consent of that person and you have informed him/her and/or given him/her the opportunity to research in regard to the use that we will make of Personal Data as provided for in this policy.

Finally, you affirm that all of the Personal Data included in the recordings or in those contents or works you create has been collected with the consent of the persons involved and that they have been informed of the usage we will make of their personal data, in accordance with this privacy policy.

**3\. YOUR DATA RETENTION TIME**

Your Personal Data will be kept for the time necessary to comply with the purposes of the usage. After that will be retained, blocked, during the necessary limitation periods, depending on the applicable legislation to comply with legal obligations.

**4\. USE OF GOOGLE USER DATA**

In Red Karaoke we use some Google services, which implies the processing of your Personal Data in the following way:

a) Google registration and identification service, so that our users can register or identify themselves with their Google accounts. Red Karaoke is responsible for the processing of said data. These services are:

• _https://www.googleapis.com/auth/userinfo.profile_. We treat the basic information of your profile (identifying data: username, gender and the thumbnail of your profile image) in order to facilitate registration, identify users and, with your permission, spread it to other users when you enter My profile of my user. This information is downloaded only once and stored in the Service's database.

• _https://www.googleapis.com/auth/userinfo.email_. We treat your user email to save it in our database when you register. We will use this email to contact you, but it will not be shared with any third party. This information is downloaded only once and stored in the Service's database.

• _https://www.googleapis.com/auth/contacts.readonly_. When you click on the "Search friends" button, you will be asked for a permission to access your contacts. When you accept, we will consult with our database, which will show if any match. We do not store this data, we do not even register it transiently, we use it only to find friends.

• _https://www.googleapis.com/auth/youtube_. We treat your identifying data only when you enter your credentials to upload your videos to YouTube. We do not store any information about you.

b) Google Services "AdMob" and "AdSense": Red Karaoke is responsible for the processing of your personal data processed in these services (IP, online identifiers).

c) Google Services "Google Analytics", "Attribution", "Optimize", "Tag Manager" and "Data Studio": Red Karaoke treats your personal data (IP, those that allow online identification and identification of clients) to through Google, acting as responsible, being Google in charge of such treatment.

**5\. ACCESS TO THE SERVICE THROUGH OTHER PLATFORMS**

You have the possibility to sign up for the service using your social networking profile (like Facebook, Google or Instagram plus). When you sign up or login through these profiles, we will use the basic information of your profile (your name, to create your username, your gender, your age, and the thumbnail to create your profile picture), all based on the performance of the contract. We will also use your email address to communicate with you.

**6\. TRANSFER AND/OR COMMUNICATION OF INFORMATION**

Your data will not be transferred to third parties located in other States members of the European economic area, except those who provide us with support services, such as payment methods or financing entities, fight against fraud entities, being the execution of the contract and compliance with current legislation that legitimizes us for such assignments. These data communications constitute access to data on behalf of third parties covered by the Law.

**7\. LINKS**

The service may include, show or display links to other websites for your convenience and information. Those websites may be managed separately from us. It is possible that these sites with links have their own privacy policies, we strongly recommend you to read them when you visit those sites. If any linked website that you visit is not of our property or under our control, we are not responsible of the content of such websites, their use or their privacy practices.

In this Service you can choose certain features that use Personal Data we share with other entities or websites (for instance, “share” on Facebook). These features, ranging from social networking tools to geographical location tools, are managed by third parties not related to us. Such third parties may use personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. Those third parties are listed on the websites where these features are provided. _We strongly recommend you to check these third-party’s privacy policies if you are going to use their features._

**8\. YOUR RIGHTS**

You have rights related to the personal information we have about you:

\- Right to confirm whether or not we are dealing with personal data that concerns you, and, in such case, request access to them.

\- Right to request rectification (when we have incomplete personal data) or deletion (when the data are no longer necessary for the purposes for which they were collected, you have withdrawn your consent or you object to the treatment, among other reasons).

\- Right to request the limitation of your treatment, in which case we will only keep them for the exercise or defense of claims.

\- In certain circumstances and for reasons related to your particular situation, you have the right to oppose the treatment. We will stop processing the data, in which case we will only keep it for the exercise or defense of claims.

\- Right to the portability of the data, in which case we will proceed to transmit your data to the person responsible.

\- Right to withdraw your consent at any time, without affecting the legality of the treatment based on the consent prior to its withdrawal.

To exercise these rights, you can contact us at the address indicated above or through the email .In any case, you must prove your identity through your National ID 

Also, if you consider that in the usage of your data has violated the regulations on data protection, you have the right to file a claim with the Spanish Agency for Data Protection, c / Jorge Juan, 6, 28001, Madrid , Spain.

**9\. INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFER**

Apart from the cases mentioned in clause 5, we may transfer your personal data to countries not belonging to the European economic area (EEA) which are located third parties who provide services to us. Thus, we will transfer internationally to the United States to manage the Service and our contractual relationship with you, but do so on the basis of a contract in accordance with clauses model approved by the Decision of the European Commission 2010/87/EC of 5 February 2010.

We will comply with the applicable legal requirements by providing appropriate protection for transfer of personal information to countries outside the European Union.

**10\. SECURITY MEASURES**

We guarantee that we have adopted the security measures of protection of the Personal Data legally required, and we have installed all the technical means and measures to avoid the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and theft of the same. , and guarantee the pseudonymization and encryption of data, its confidentiality, integrity, availability and resilience, the ability to restore availability and access to them, as well as a process of regular verification, evaluation and assessment of the effectiveness of measures to guarantee the safety of the treatment.

However, you should be aware that security measures on the Internet are not impregnable. As long as we require you to provide us with relevant information (such as, for example, your National Identity Document or your credit card number), that information is subject to encryption processes according to the standards in the market. The data that is sent from that moment on will be transmitted in a totally secure way. Additionally, we have incorporated measures to guarantee the integrity of the data and the correction in its use.

**11\. COOKIES AND OTHER STORAGE DEVICES**

**What is a cookie?**

A cookie is a file that is downloaded to your computer, Smartphone, Tablet or any other electronic device when you access certain websites. Cookies are necessary to make your navigation easier and improve your experience within this Service.

Such is the case that, to use the website, the use of cookies and other own and third-party storage devices with similar characteristics is necessary. Both are used with the purpose of offering a better service through the different browsers used.

Cookies used in websites are only associated with the browser of a specific computer (an anonymous User), and do not provide by themselves User’s first or last name. The User has the option to configure their browser to be notified on screen about reception of cookies and to stop cookies installation on their hard drive.

**How are cookies managed?**

By using the website, you agree and allow us to host these cookies on your computer or device for the purposes set out herein.

If you choose not to accept our cookies, you can continue to use our website in the usual way, although it is possible that your user experience will be slightly affected.

**What types of cookies exist and what are they for?**

_Analysis cookies_ : They allow us to track and analyze your behavior and that of other Service users. We use the information collected by these cookies to measure the Service activity and to develop Service users’ navigation profiles in order to improve the service. 

Google Analytics: [www.google.com/analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics)

_Advertising cookies_ : They allow us to efficiently manage the advertising spaces included in the Service.

_Behavioral advertising cookies_ : They allow us to efficiently manage the advertising spaces we have included. These cookies store information about your behavior (and that of other users) obtained through continued observance of your navigation habits, which allows to develop your specific profile and show you ads according to your preferences.

<https://www.google.com/adsense/start/>

_Cookies to exchange social content_ : They are used to identify content shared with other websites.

<https://es-es.facebook.com/>

<https://www.google.com/intl/es/+/learnmore/>

We also use cookies to measure and track different marketing campaigns that we create or are created by third parties hired by us.

**How can you uninstall or manage cookies?**

During a browser installation or update you can allow or decline cookies installation; you can even not accept any of the cookies having the option to be notified whenever you receive a cookie. Thus, to allow, know, block or delete cookies installed on your computer you can do it by modifying the settings on the web browser installed on your computer.

Information about how to do this can be found at the following links:

<https://support.mozilla.org/es/kb/Borrar%20cookies> for Firefox.

[https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=es&answer=95647](https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=es&answer=95647) for Chrome.

<https://windows.microsoft.com/es-es/windows7/how-to-manage-cookies-in-internet-explorer-9> for Explorer.

<https://support.apple.com/kb/ph5042> for Safari.

If you want to get more accurate and complete information about all the cookies we use on this website, their purpose, duration and whether they are own or third-party cookies, please click [here](https://www.redkaraoke.com/terms/en/cookies)

**12\. PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY UPDATES**

This Policy may be regularly updated with prior notice and enough time to reflect changes in our practices regarding personal information. We will post a prominent notice to notify you of any significant changes to our Policy. Every installation or update of any of the applications that are part of the Red Karaoke Service you must accept the new Privacy Policy in case it has been modified since your last installation or update.

**13\. HOW TO CONTACT US**

You can get in touch with us if you have any questions or if you want to exercise the rights of access, rectification, portability, cancellation, limitation and opposition signed by writing to the attention of "customer support departament" to the above address or by e-mail
